homepagesforhomerooms.com 2011-12-23

# Yahoo! Privacy Policy

Promotions (such as contests, sweepstakes or giveaways) that are hosted on Yahoo! may be sponsored by Yahoo!, may be co-sponsored by Yahoo! and another company, or may be sponsored by companies other than Yahoo!. Yahoo! may also sponsor or co-sponsor promotions hosted by third parties. 

Information Collection and Use Practices

  * When you enter a promotion hosted or sponsored by Yahoo! and/or our partners, you are asked to provide registration information, which may include your name, address, and email address. Depending on the promotion, you may also be asked to provide additional information, some of which may be optional, in order to participate.
  * Yahoo! may pre-populate promotion registration information from your Yahoo! account when you are signed in, but this registration information will not be communicated to any party until you chose to submit. Prior to submission, you may edit the registration form to alter any of the pre-populated information. 
  * We (or our representatives) may contact you in connection with a promotion you have entered in order to update you of your status, administer the promotion, or for other purposes specified in the promotion rules.

Information Sharing and Disclosure Practices

  * Third parties that host promotions may collect and use your information alone or in conjunction with Yahoo!. If information is collected and used by a third party, please review the third party’s Privacy Policy to learn about its information practices.
  * If you decide to share information, there will be notice prior to the time of data collection or transfer. Notice may be provided on the entry form and/or in the promotion rules.
  * Yahoo! occasionally partners with ePrize, LLC to provide you with access to both Yahoo! and third party-sponsored promotions. For more information on how ePrize collects and uses your information, please visit the [ePrize Privacy Policy](http://eprize.com/privacy-policy/). 

Practices Regarding Cookies

  * Some promotion sites may use Cookies in order to track your progress or number of entries in a promotion. Please see more information about Cookies [here](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/cookies/).

Other

  * When you participate in a promotion, you are subject to the Official Rules of that promotion, which may contain information about the privacy practices associated with that promotion.

This page describes current Yahoo! practices with respect to promotions. This information may change as Yahoo! revises this service by adding or removing features or using different service providers. To find out how Yahoo! treats your personal information, please visit our [Privacy Policy](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/).
